All right.
So congratulations on finishing up the structural design patents and now we are onto our last group
of design veterans and that is behavioral design patents.
So Design Patterns in this group they revolve around designing the interaction between objects and classes
and by designing these interactions in a certain way we can solve a multitude of problems.
And I assure you that this is one of the most exciting group of design patterns and you will use most
of these design patterns almost regularly.
So let's look at the list of design patterns.
OK so this is a lot less but I assure you that you are probably already using most of these.
So chain of response with the this is the first one.
If you have every word with servlet in Java then you have used chain of responsibility because all these
overlit filters follow this design.
If you have worked with collections in Java then you have used with work with iterator greater design
Bahan observer and visiter are some of the most used patterns because they solve specific problems that
are very common.
All right.
So let's start with chain of responsibility in the next video.