Or I'd support solutions on finishing up your first group of design parents you now have all the tools
that are needed to solve problems that are related to creating objects from glasses.
Now it's time to jump to the next group in our design patterns study and that is the structural design
patterns so designers that belong to this group they deal with how we can arrange our classes and objects
in order to get some functionality or behavior are there.
So do we mean by that so we can use composition and we can use inheritance and when we combine these
two powerful features and create arrangements using these two features of object oriented programming
we can get some really interesting behavior out of our objects and classes and using these arrangements
we can solve some really common problems that we will face in your real life.
Devlopment So here is a list of design patterns that we are going to study here and these design problems
solves some very interesting problems.
For example let's say you want to provide a method level security to your objects so you want to make
sure that whoever is calling your object's method must have performed an art indication.
Let's say you want to use or simplify use of your subsystem so you have these multiple classes designed
that carry out complicated functionality.
But now it is becoming quite a tiresome or tedious for the client code to use all these classes.
So you can simplify your entire subsystem using a single plus.
So these are some of the examples of problems that design patterns in this group trying to solve.
All right.
So we're going to start with adapter and see you in the next one.